Hello.
This is Kyamai from Bartender's Time!
We have a new addition to our morning crew.
Rah!
We have sweet potatoes.
She loves the tip of a baked sweet potato.
She is an idol who loves sweet potatoes beyond measure!
Kanmon Cinema
Please say a few words.
There is a sweet potato
Tick City
Here you go.
Trip Trip Kitakyushu
Next is Trip Trip Kitakyushu!
We've added a new member to our team, and we're going to make Kitakyushu even more energetic and exciting!
Trip Trip Kitakyushu's new partner will be joining us this time!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
Hello!
I'm Ai Kiyama from the Batten Girls Club.
Nice to meet you!
Dar!
Da-da!
That's what it means, right?
That's right.
This is Ai Kiyama of the Kyushu-based idol group Batten Shoujo-tai!
Batten Shoujo-tai has released songs themed on various prefectures in Kyushu so far!
The song "Oisa" was inspired by the Wakata Yone Yamakasa festival.
It has been viewed more than 5 million times on YouTube and has become a hot topic nationwide.
In addition, the momentum has not stopped overseas.
At a live performance in Paris, they filled 1,800 seats.
They are a group that is attracting attention at home and abroad.
Do you have a catchphrase?
My name is Kyamai, and I am the leader of the group "O-imo o tajinode sansenri dance.
Taste the sweet potato for 3,000 miles.
Yes, I love sweet potatoes, and they are in season right now!
I see, so you are a dance leader.
Yes, I have been dancing since elementary school and I love it very much!
So let's dance together!
Dancing?
Now, right now.
You're dancing now?
What do you mean?
It's nice to meet you two.
This time...
Kitakyushu is often used as a filming location.
Is that so?
Yes, Kitakyushu is very famous as a filming location.
Many movies and TV dramas have been filmed here.
In particular, large-scale filming of bombing scenes, etc.
Kitakyushu's full support is the only reason why it is possible.
Kitakyushu attracts the attention of film crews from all over the country.
I heard that the central market here is also a filming location for a movie.
Right here on this street.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Masaki Suda...
Mr. Masaki Suda filmed here
This is where they filmed the movie starring Masaki Suda.
This is where they filmed the movie "Tomogui" starring Masaki Suda.
It's hard to express the realistic shutterbug district in a movie set.
The realistic shutterbug street is a good spot not only for movies, but also for photo shoots.
So we decided to go for it.
I'd like to take a picture with depth, so please go that way.
You can enter here.
It's retro.
It's nice.
The shutters give it a nice retro feel.
That's really nice, isn't it?
Retro.
I wonder what the shutter looks like.
It looks like a computer.
It sure looks like a computer.
It really looks good.
It's our first time on location, so the two of us are still a little awkward.
Now, we're going to walk around the harbor.
And here's where Ai-chan unexpectedly shows up.
There's a sweet potato!
They look so delicious!
I love sweet potatoes, don't you?
I know the legend of the sweet potato.
Yes, I know.
A famous restaurant in 19 states.
Looks delicious.
Which do you prefer?
What do you think?
I love sweet potatoes.
Warm.
Ai loves sweet potatoes more than rice sandwiches!
She bought it without hesitation!
What's going on?
It's a sweet potato!
A sweet potato.
It's got so much meat in it!
It smells so good!
A baked sweet potato.
Delicious!
It smells so good!
It's so soft!
I've never had a soft one before.
I like the tip of the baked sweet potato.
I feel like everything is packed in there.
That's where all of the baked sweet potato is packed?
I didn't know that.
That's where I like to start.
I like to end it with that.
That's right.
After enjoying my favorite sweet potato
we went to the observatory where we could see the Kanmon Bridge.
Why did we come here?
After all, you want to look good nowadays, don't you?
Kitakyushu is hosting the "Kanmon Cinematic City
Kanmon Cinemastic City
There were a lot of things here.
Please take a look at it.
Kanmon Cinemastic City
Voila!
There are many spots in the Kanmon Straits area that look like they could be in a scene from a movie
The site that introduces these scenic spots is called
The site is called "Kanmon Cinematic City".
They all look great, don't they?
The two of us decided to take a lesson from the female models and try our hand at taking a picture!
Three female models decided to watch a movie.
Then you're a little closer.
There are three trees.
Yes, sir.
What? I don't know why.
Kannon Kagamiza. It's tiny.
So tiny!
The picture is big, but...
Why is it so small?
Why does it look so small?
Is it small?
Is this in the picture?
No, it's not in the picture.
Why not? What about Kanmon Bridge?
Wait a minute.
Took me 10 minutes of trial and error.
Zoom in?
Zooming in.
It's true, it's bigger now.
Does it look good?
And... Okay.
Is it done?
Is the Kanmon family getting bigger?
It's getting so big!
Yes!
Bigger than before!
We got the answer.
Good.
You're holding him.
Well, that's new.
I like the way you're exploring... the distance between us.
It's still a little awkward.
It's okay... you're hitting all the right notes.
That exchange...
There's a new one, Ai Kiyama.
Ai Kiyama, the sweet-potato lover.
Yes, a sweet potato lover.
I hear it's all in the tip.
Please try it!
Mochi is good, and the warm ones are always hot.
Yes, it's hot, and the cold one is quite cool.
The cold ones are cool and tasty!
Imotenbushi is delicious, isn't it?
It's delicious, isn't it?
I love it!
It's a vending machine, so please try it when you go there!
And then...
Kitakyushu Cinematic City Kitakyushu Cinematic City
Kitakyushu Cinematic City
Kitakyushu International Film Festival will be held from next month!
And at the festival, there will be a lot of actors and actresses.
It's amazing!
They're going to be filming, so please give them some time.
That's right.
The director, Daio Matsui, the director, and all the actors...
I'm sure the Kitakyushu International Film Festival will be a great success!
I hope you all have a great time at the festival!
That's all for Trip Trip Kitakyushu!